thetaoofbadass.com 2019-03-13

# thetaoofbadass.com

**Privacy Policy**

**Last Updated Tuesday, June 19, 2018**

We at The Tao of Badass are committed to protecting your personal information. 

Each time you visit our websites or provide us with information, you are accepting the practices as described in the policy at that time. Please review this policy from time to time as we may update it periodically. If you have entered into a separate agreement with The Tao of Badass (a licensing agreement, nondisclosure agreement, etc.) that agreement may include additional relevant information.

**California residents, please also see the "Note To California Residents" Section for additional rights that apply to you.**

**Information We Collect From You**

To provide you with products and services, we may collect personal information (i.e. name, user name, shipping address, phone number, email address), financial information (i.e. credit card numbers and billing addresses), and demographic information (i.e. zip code, age). We retain personal information no longer than is necessary for business purposes or legal requirements. If you do not provide certain account information, or withdraw consent for us to use it, we may not be able to provide some services to you.

Voluntary submissions of personal information can occur for various reasons, such as if you request to receive information about our services, or if you subscribe to one of our mailing lists.

If you subscribe to one of our mailing lists, we generally collect your name, email address, and optionally your telephone or other information if you provide it to us so we can customize your experience and better serve your needs.

**Children Under the Age of 16**

Children under the age of 16 are required to provide consent from a holder of parental responsibility. This person may review the child's personal information, withdraw consent to use it, or have it deleted, by contacting [support@thetaoofbadass.com](mailto:support@socialtrainingcompany.com). 

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

We use information you provide, like names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and sometimes credit card information when such information is voluntarily submitted by our visitors as well as to deliver the services you have requested, to contact you when necessary in connection with those service requests, to send you information regarding your order or requested services, and to prevent fraud and spam. Most of your customer information is stored in a third-party Customer Relationship Manager (CRM) system called Pipedrive via a service called Clickfunnels, and not directly on our servers.

Your credit card information is not stored by us, and is instead passed to a payment processor called Stripe via a service called Clickfunnels. 

We automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This includes your IP address, your browser and operating system, and details of how you used our website.

Cookies are text files that are used by your computer's web browser to store your preferences, and enable us to enhance your user experience with our site. Third party retargeting networks may also use cookies to display our advertisements to you on other sites.� You can learn more about how to opt-out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/)[DG1] .

Please note that you do have the option to configure most web browsers to NOT accept cookies.

However, be aware that disabling cookies may keep you from having access to some functions or services on our site or the web-hosted software that runs on our site. 

Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret web browser-based "Do Not Track" signals other than cookies, we do not currently respond to "Do Not Track" signals that are undefined.

We are waiting for the online industry to develop a common protocol for how to treat DNT signals. In the meantime, you can use the range of other tools we provide to control data collection and use, including those described herein. 

If you opt in to emails about our products, offers, updates, and events, we may send you emails about these topics on behalf of ourselves and/or our affiliates. You can opt out of non-transactional emails by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email communication, or by emailing [support@thetaoofbadass.com](mailto:support@socialtrainingcompany.com). You can customize your email and other preferences (such as the lists you are subscribed to) by following the instructions contained in the Section entitled "Access to and Control of Your Personal Information". We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do.

By submitting your email address, you also agree to allow us to use your email address for custom audience targeting on sites like Facebook, where we display custom advertising to specific people who have opted-in to receive communications from us.

If you visit this site with an open ID (such as Facebook), you may also be sharing and integrating data with third-party social media sites, and we may track aggregate data about the number of visits to this site with an open ID, the number of items "liked" on this site, or items on this site that you choose to share with a third-party social media site.

If you wish to stop seeing ads from us on Facebook, you can turn off the ad by using the following steps:

From within Facebook, go to the advertisement you want to turn off. ii. Click on the drop-down arrow in the top corner of the ad (that may be in the top right corner or top left corner). iii. Click on "Hide ad". 

You can also customize the ads you see in Facebook across all advertisers by using the following steps:

Log in to your Facebook account and click "settings". ii. Click on "Ads". iii. On that page you will see a list of options you can choose to limit and/or block the information Facebook shows to advertisers. 

If you wish to stop seeing ads from us in Google Ads, you can turn off the ad by using the following steps:

Go to the advertisement you want to turn off. ii. Click on the x in the top left corner. iii. Click on "Stop seeing thisad". 

Other ad platforms we may use in the future have similar ways you can turn off any ad from us to stop seeing it.

In addition, you agree that by submitting your telephone contact information on our site and/or registering to receive the product and/or service offered herein, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry, and/or an application for the purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (ATSR), 16 CFR �310 et seq. and any applicable state and local "do not call" regulations. We retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR and the applicable state regulations.

If you enter information into our websites outside of secure transactions, the content you provide may be visible to the public along with any associated username. Do not post sensitive personal information such as your address or credit card number outside of secure transactions on our sites. Users posting messages to our sites automatically grant The Tao of Badass the royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, nonexclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, sublicense, copy and distribute such messages throughout the world in any media.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which The Tao of Badass or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

**How We Share Your Personal Information**

In some cases, it is necessary for us to provide information particular to you to a third party.

�         When you give us a billing address or credit card information, we provide it to a credit card processor to check your qualifications and to charge you for products and services you order from us. By making a purchase or engaging in another activity on our websites that uses financial information, you consent to our providing your financial information to third parties as necessary to process your transactions. If you do not provide this information, or withdraw consent to our sharing it for the above purpose, we cannot process your orders.

�         When you give us an address, we may provide it to shipping services in order to determine shipping rates and to ship your packages. If the address is within the United States, we provide it to an address verification service for standardization. If the address is within the state of Washington, we provide it to a geolocation service to determine your tax district so that we can correctly charge sales tax. If the address is outside of the United States, we may ask for a phone number; this is provided to the shipper per their requirement. If you do not provide this information, or withdraw consent to our sharing it for the above purpose, we cannot process your orders.

This information will be used by the partner solely to provide access to and pricing information for that partner's products. If you do not provide this information, or withdraw consent to our sharing it for the above purpose, our partners' ability to provide access to and beneficial pricing information for these products may be limited.

We may disclose your personal information to other parties if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us or our sites; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The Tao of Badass and its web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The Tao of Badass, its web sites, or the public.

Other parties such as advertising partners and analytics companies may also be collecting information about your online activity across various websites over time. The information collected by those third parties may include identifiers that allow those third parties to tailor the ads that they serve to your computer or other device.

The Tao of Badass will not share your personal information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions stated above.

**Information Other Websites Collect From You**

While many websites share information about your browsing activities with other services, The Tao of Badass does not. Some parts of our services are hosted by companies that may collect usage data for the purpose of providing and improving service.

Please be aware that there are links from our site to other websites operated by other parties where our privacy policy does not apply. We encourage you to review their privacy policies, and remind you that we are not responsible for their actions.

**Access to and Control of Your Personal Information**

You have the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current.

You can also contact [support@thetaoofbadass.com](mailto:support@socialtrainingcompany.com) to:

�         Ask for a copy of any personal information you have already given us. (See details below).

�         Ask to have your personal information deleted (i.e. "forgotten") from our databases. (See details below) .

�         Opt into or out of emails about The Tao of Badass products, official licensed products, special offers, updates, and events. (See details below).

�         Opt into or out of emails containing marketing messages (See details below).

If you wish to request that we export your data (such as for porting it to another vendor), please send an email to [support@thetaoofbadass.com](mailto:support@socialtrainingcompany.com) with the subject line "Export My Data", and explain in the body of the email that you are asking for a data export.� We have a standard data export format that we will provide and are not able to create custom exports.

To protect user privacy, you must send such a request from the account information we have on file or the request will not be honored.� 

If you wish to request that we forget you from our database, please send an email to [support@thetaoofbadass.com](mailto:support@socialtrainingcompany.com) with the subject line "Forget Me", and explain in the body of the email that you are asking to have your personal data deleted.� To protect user privacy, you must send such a request from the account information we have on file or the request will not be honored.

We reserve the right to retain any data that we are required to maintain under applicable laws.� (Some data will be anonymized rather than deleted; this means that some of the data will be held in a form that cannot be connected to you personally.) Please be aware that once we delete your data, we will be unable to "undelete" it. (Among other things, this means you will be unable to redownload any previous purchases, as we will no longer be able to connect that purchase to you.) 

If you are a subscriber to one of our mailing lists, you can customize your information and the mailing lists you have subscribed to at any time by simply clicking the link called "Manage Subscription"" at the bottom of any email you receive from us. That will take you to a preferences center where you can update your information and communication preferences.

**Notice of Rights**

Subjects in the European Union are advised of the following rights; The Tao of Badass gladly provides the same opportunities to subjects outside the European Union. (You may have other rights.)

�         You may request access to and rectification or erasure of personal data concerning you.

�         You may request restriction of data processing concerning you.

�         You may request the personal data which you have provided us concerning you, and you may transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from us.

�         You may object at any time to our processing of personal data concerning you and you may withdraw your consent for future processing.

�         If you are a subject in the European Union, and you believe that The Tao of Badass's processing of personal data relating to you infringes the EU's General Data Protection Regulation, you may lodge a complaint with your Member State's designated supervisory authority.

**IP Addresses**

We may use your IP address to help prevent fraud, to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and to offer you products and services.

**Commitment to Data Security**

All information collected from you is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. Furthermore, employees, contractors, and vendors who have access to your personally identifiable information in connection with providing services for us are required to keep the information confidential.

We use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, and we do everything we can to protect user information offline. Unfortunately, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we take reasonable measures to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**Changes to This Policy**

The Tao of Badass will occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the page. For material changes to this policy, The Tao of Badass will notify you by placing prominent notice on our web sites, and may contact you via email.

**Contact**

If you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy, or about your dealings with our websites, contact:

The Tao of Badass

8605 Santa Monica Blvd #21631

Los Angeles, CA 90069 USA

**Severability**

If any part of this privacy policy is held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed in a manner consistent with applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties, and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect.

**Note to California Residents**

If you live in the State of California, under the California Civil Code, you have the right to request that companies who conduct business in California provide you with a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed Personal Information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. 

Alternatively, the law provides that if a company has a privacy policy that gives either an opt-out (often referred to as "unsubscribe") or opt-in choice for use of your Personal Information by third parties (such as advertisers or affiliated companies) for marketing purposes, that the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options. 

This site qualifies for the alternative option; it has a comprehensive privacy policy and provides you with details on how you may either opt-out or opt-in to the use of your Personal Information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your Personal Information for marketing purposes during the preceding year. 

If you are a California resident and want to request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, you must send a request to the following address with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). Please send an email to the Privacy Administrator at [support@thetaoofbadass.com](mailto:support@socialtrainingcompany.com), or you may contact us via regular mail at: 

The Tao of Badass

8605 Santa Monica Blvd #21631

Los Angeles, CA 90069 USA

**All requests sent via regular mail must be labeled "Your California Privacy Rights" on the email subject line or envelope and clearly stated on the actual request**. For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please include your zip code for our own recordkeeping. 

**We do not accept requests via the telephone or by facsimile**. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.
